<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mikeroySoft.com</title>
    <link>http://mikeroysoft.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mikeroySoft.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:43:31 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://mikeroysoft.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thing</title>
      <link>http://mikeroysoft.com/derpurl/thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:43:31 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikeroysoft.com/derpurl/thing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Derpurl</title>
      <link>http://mikeroysoft.com/derpurl/derpurl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:43:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikeroysoft.com/derpurl/derpurl/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Derpurl</title>
      <link>http://mikeroysoft.com/derp/derpurl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:42:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikeroysoft.com/derp/derpurl/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About_me</title>
      <link>http://mikeroysoft.com/about/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:36:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikeroysoft.com/about/about_me/</guid>
      <description>A wise man once told me that success is part opportunity, part timing, part preparation, and finally, part luck. I add to that list risk and willingness to embrace change.
Coming from a unique and diverse background, I often struggled with a career path that didn’t quite fit who I was. I was very happy as the SysAdmin (Systems Administrator) at a small data center in Toronto, when a unique opportunity came across my lap. That opportunity quickly fell through: the company presented me a false view of their own stability and went belly-up two months after I relocated from Toronto, about 20 days from Christmas. So, I went work for a local Apple support center.
But in 2009, opportunity happened. A teammate of mine got an interview at VMware for a new Fusion support team, and they needed Apple experts. A thorough interview later, they offered me a position, and we moved to create what I consider the best support team with which I’ve had the pleasure of working with.
We not only had a strong technical group (most of whom by now have moved on to more technical roles in and outside of VMware), but we also had a synergy that I’ve not seen outside of VMware Global Support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New_blog</title>
      <link>http://mikeroysoft.com/blog/2019-06/new_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:35:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikeroysoft.com/blog/2019-06/new_blog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test_blog</title>
      <link>http://mikeroysoft.com/posts/blog/test_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 20:33:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikeroysoft.com/posts/blog/test_blog/</guid>
      <description>Blog draft Here is a draft blog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>http://mikeroysoft.com/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 18:17:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mikeroysoft.com/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Frist Toast! Just switching blogging platforms again&amp;hellip; because why not&amp;hellip; Go seems all the rage so we&amp;rsquo;re trying out Hugo. I like the different workflow&amp;hellip; I get to use git to keep just about everything under control, and it looks like it should scale well (cuz I&amp;rsquo;m blowin up, you see&amp;hellip;;).
So here&amp;rsquo;s some initial content to see how this thing goes&amp;hellip; if so, I&amp;rsquo;ll go through the exercize of copying over all my old content, and take things from there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>